CONTACT ME AT

Poise, ID | 208-484-2107

taylorberry019@gmail.com

https://github.com/tberry019

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/
taylormberry/

WEB DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

- JAVASCRIPT
- C#
- HTML5 & CSS
- NODE.JS
- MONGODB
- AUTH0
- BOOTSTRAP
- WEB API/HTTP

LICENSES & CERTIFICATES

Certified ScrumMaster | 2021 Scrum Alliance - 001263052

EDUCATION

- Boise CodeWorks, Boise, ID | 2022 Software Engineering
- University of Idaho, Moscow, ID | 2014

 Bachelors of Science

TAYLOR BERRY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Enthusiastic professional with a strong work ethic and lively attitude. Excited to conquer new opportunities and lead a successful team to carve our place within the company. Confident that my honed skills, and personal experiences mixed with my love for working with people will materialize into a collaborative team of innovation with a healthy work dynamic that reflects the core values of this company.

SKILLS

- Team oriented mindset so to lean into open communication and opportunities to learn.
- Applying time managing skills to maintain an efficient balance between problem solving and seeking support.
- Experienced in Scrum methodology that applies in todays professional environment.
- Well developed customer service skills, able to communicate white actively listening resulting in a more positive and diffused situation.

EXPERIENCE

Web Development Student Codeworks

Boise, ID

- Learned new, industry relevant languages and techniques in a fast paced/work like environment.
- Implemented skills learned into building fully functioning applications.
- Simulating industry standards with partner coding, while working towards needed goals in order to meet deadlines.
- Problem solving skills, revolving around detail orientation and critical thinking to spot discrepancies and solutions for code.

Escrow Assistant/Funder TitleOne Corporation

Boise, ID | Jan 2021 - Sept 2021

 Presented loan documents and other records for signing and returned loan documents to lender after signing and following up on funding conditions.

APPLICATIONS

Tower

Event planner for users to create and attend events. Vue.js, Vuerouter, Node.js, MongoDB, MongoOse, Auth0, FullStack Development

Inspire

Task saver, weather app, clock, motivational quote, and beautiful scenery to keep you motivated. API, Node, MVC, Bootstrap. Fullstack Development

Keeper

Social Network app that allows users to visually share and discover new interests. C#, Vue.Js, Vue-Router, DotNet WebApi, AuthO, Dapper as ORM, and My SQL. Fullstack Development.

EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

- Reviewed real estate purchase contracts, ensuring they are complete and requesting any missing information.
- Performed preliminary audits and determined or obtained any necessary items to clear a title.
- Prepared estimated closing statements for officer to review.
- Maintained files, recording appropriate documentation, sent checks once closing was complete and transmitted documents to the lender.

Accounting Assistant TitleOne Corporation

Boise, ID | Jul 2015 - Jan 2021

- Applied principles of accounting to prepare, scope, and manage financial projects, transactions, and budgeting reports across all areas of the company.
- Verified and approved outgoing wire transfers for all trust accounts to ensure they stay on budget.
- Posted, reviewed, and monitored accounts receivable and payable.
- Recorded and applied payments received on outstanding invoices.
- Reviewed and posted all invoices, bills and expenses in the accounting software platform for TitleOne.
- Posted daily revenue to daily report making sure report matched the accounting software system.

Driver/Marketing TitleOne Corporation

Boise, ID | Jul 2015 - Jul 2015

- As the consumer facing business entity for title and escrow I was responsible for the exchange of loan packages, title commitments, commission checks, listing packages and other related documents.
- Hand-deliver these items and establish positive rapport with existing clients in efforts to both maintain and strengthen relationships.

Sales Representative

Ace Hardware

Moscow, ID | Sept 2013 - May 3014

 Worked with customers to determine purchasing needs and direct them to appropriate products to enhance service and satisfaction.